allscholarships.info 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy – AllScholarships

Your privacy is very important to us. At AllScholarships we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

It is allScholarship’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

**Website Visitors**

Like most websites, AllScholarships collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use this website.

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. AllScholarships only discloses logged in user and commenters IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to websites choose to interact with us in ways that require AllScholarships to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that AllScholarships gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive AllScholarships updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, AllScholarships collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with AllScholarships. AllScholarships does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

AllScholarships may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors. For instance, we may monitor the most popular pages on the site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, personally-identifying information other than as described below will not be disclosed.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

AllScholarships discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AllScholarships’s behalf or to provide services available at AllScholarships.info, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using AllScholarships’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. AllScholarships will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, AllScholarships discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when AllScholarships believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AllScholarships, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an this website and have supplied your email address, AllScholarships may send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with our services. If you send us a request (for example via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. AllScholarships takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AllScholarships uses cookies to help AllScholarships identify and track visitors, their usage of AllScholarships website, and their website access preferences. AllScholarships visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using AllScholarships’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of AllScholarships’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners such as Google Adsense, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by AllScholarships and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Comments**

Comments and other content submitted to Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, AllScholarships may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in AllScholarships’s sole discretion. AllScholarships encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
